gopollgo.com 2012-05-03

# Privacy Policy | GoPollGo | Online Polls

These Terms of Use were last updated on _October 26th, 2010_

Your privacy is important to us. GoPollGo.com has prepared these privacy and security policies ("Statement") so you may better understand how GoPollGo.com ("our Website") may use your personal information in connection with our Website and services, as well as how it protects your information against unauthorized use. Please take the time to review this Statement and contact us using the Contact Information below with any questions or concerns.

### Collection of Information

GoPollGo.com may ask you to register and provide personal information in certain instances, such as when you choose to personalize your use of our Website or when you contact our customer support. Personally identifiable information that we may collect may include, but is not limited to, your name, e-mail address, phone number and address. GoPollGo.com may also collect demographic information such as your age, gender, zip code, level of education, household income, and interests as well as your ip address and location (city, state, latitude, longitude, division, subdivision, country, continent, etc).

If you choose not to register, you can still use most of our Website. Unfortunately, you will not be able to access areas that require registration.

#### Children's Personal Information

GoPollGo.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from users under the age of 13. If we find out that we have such personal information, we will take reasonable steps to delete it.

#### Website Usage Information

GoPollGo.com tracks navigational data (log files, server logs, click-stream) and information about how our Website is used by you (through cookies, Internet tags, or web beacons). We also collect information such as the URL of the Website you previously visited and the time of day that you use our Website. GoPollGo.com also keeps track of the pages you visit within our Website as well as any transaction details (downloads, orders, requests, or referrals). You can set your browser to notify you when a cookie is sent, or to refuse or delete cookies altogether, but in such cases certain features of our Website might not function as expected.

### How We Use Your Information

#### Personal Information

GoPollGo.com collects, integrates, and uses your personal information to help enhance and personalize your use of our Website and the services that we may offer. This information also allows us to provide you with targeted content, information. We also use anonymous and aggregated data to create statistics and reports for various business purposes. We may aggregate anonymous data and share with or sell to our customers or GoPollGo.com partners.

GoPollGo.com may also use your information to communicate with you, but only after you give your express permission for such communication. The exception is the case of "service e-mails," which we use to communicate with you regarding the system itself or your use of the system. Examples include: communication around system downtimes, announcements regarding the launch of new services, responses to customer service enquires, and messages regarding the completion of transactions you have initiated.

#### Website Usage Information

The website usage information we collect (e.g., cookies, Internet tags, web beacons, etc.) is used by GoPollGo.com to monitor the operation, technical functions, and quality of our Website and services. This information is also used to provide general statistics regarding use of our Website. We may also use such information for research or improvements of our Website and the services we offer you. This data is also used by GoPollGo.com to deliver customized content to you when your online behavior indicates that you are interested in a particular subject area.

Disclosure of Data

GoPollGo.com keeps your personally identifiable information confidential. We do not disclose it to third parties or others that do not have a need to know such information, except under certain circumstances. Set forth below are various circumstances under which GoPollGo.com may share your personal information:

  * Certain of our employees and independent contractors have access to your personally identifiable information for the sole purpose of helping us run our business. These employees and contractors have confidentiality and security obligations.
  * We may disclose your personally identifiable information in the event that we sell this Website or substantial parts of our business, provided that the buyer agrees to comply with this Statement.
  * We may share your information with affiliated companies or strategic alliance partners, provided they comply with this Statement.
  * Although we do not provide your personally identifiable information to our customers and partners, we do aggregate and supply them with anonymous data (for example, "20,000 members of GoPollGo.com are living in Santa Clara County" or "53% of people who voted on this poll are Females between the ages of 18 and 24").
  * If you post any information in public areas of our Website, such as chat rooms, comments and message boards, it will be available to the public and we may reuse and republish such information at our discretion and in accordance with our Terms of Use.
  * We may also share your personally identifiable information to respond to law enforcement requests, court orders, or other legal processes; or if we believe that such disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent, or respond to illegal activities, fraud, physical threats to you or others; or as otherwise required by any applicable law or regulation.
  * Before we disclose your personally identifiable information for other reasons, we will first obtain your consent, via e-mail, click-through, an online opportunity to enter your preference, or some other manner.

In the event that we disclose your personally identifiable information as set forth above, we will require third party organizations to protect and maintain your personally identifiable information in compliance with the terms and conditions of this Statement.

#### Prohibited Disclosures

Except as set forth above, GoPollGo.com will not disclose your personally identifiable information to any third party without your explicit consent. In addition, GoPollGo.com will not sell, rent, or otherwise disclose GoPollGo.com's e-mail list or address list except as explicitly set forth in this Privacy Policy.

If your personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, or e-mail or postal address), or if you no longer desire our service, we provide a way for you to correct, update, or delete/deactivate your personally identifiable information. This can be done by visiting the Settings page on our Website or by e-mailing our Customer Support service at support@GoPollGo.com.

#### Protection of Information -- Security

GoPollGo.com is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of up-to-date security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store any personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access. These systems are located in controlled facilities.

You should keep in mind that no Internet communication is ever completely secure or error-free.

### Changes To This Statement

We may periodically update this Statement to reflect changes in our services and policies. When we post changes to this Statement, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this Statement. If there are material changes to the Statement or in how GoPollGo.com will use your personal information, we will notify you either by posting a prominent notice prior to implementing the change or by sending you a direct notification. We encourage you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

### Contact Information

If you have questions or complaints regarding this Statement, you should first contact us through by emailing support@GoPollGo.com with any questions or concerns. All customer requests will be formally reviewed by GoPollGo.com.

Chief Privacy Officer  
GoPollGo.com  
460 S California Ave  
Palo Alto, CA 94306

### Terms of Use

Note also that your use of the Website is subject to our Terms of Use.
